<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Python on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</title>
    <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-tw</language><atom:link href="https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3.1. Basic Data Access Methods</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch3/ch3.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch3/ch3.1/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents What is pyCIOT? pyCIOT Basics Installation Import Package Data Access Air Quality Data Get all project codes: Air().get_source() Get all stations: Air().get_station() Get data of a station: Air().get_data() Water Resource Data Get all project codes: Water().get_source() Get all stations: Water().get_station() Get data of a station: Water().get_data() Earthquake Data Get all project codes: Quake().get_source() Get all stations: Quake().get_station() Get data of a station: Quake().get_data() Get data of an earthquake eventQuake().</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4.1. Time Series Data Processing</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch4/ch4.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch4/ch4.1/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Goal Package Installation and Importing Data Access Air Quality Data Water Level Data Meteorological Data Data Visualization Data Resample Moving Average Multi-line Charts Calendar Heatmap Data Quality Inspection Outlier Detection Change Point Detection) Missing Data Handling Data Decomposition References Time series data refers to information that is organized based on when it occurred or was recorded. This data is often set at regular time intervals, like every five minutes or hourly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5.1. Geospatial Filtering</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/ch5.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/ch5.1/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Intersect Buffer Multi-ring buffer Distance matrix Brief Summary In the past, if we wanted to learn about things like air quality, earthquakes, or floods, we usually depended on information from public sources or experts to understand how widespread and intense these events were.
Imagine you want to check the air quality around your home. The Taiwan Air Quality Monitoring Network, managed by the Environmental Protection Administration Executive Yuan, is a key source of this info.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.1. Machine Learning Preliminaries</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch6/ch6.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch6/ch6.1/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Preamble Classification Clustering Package Installation and Importing Case 1: Location Type Classification of Air Quality Sensors Data Cleansing Outlier removal Train data and test data Using the pre-built Sklearn models Case 2: Clustering of Air Quality Sensors Data download and preprocessing Dynamic Time Warping (DTW) K-Mean clustering Correlation between data clusters and geographical locations Correlation between data clusters and wind directions Case 3: Clustering and Classification Application of Water and Meteorological Data Data download and preprocessing Correlation of flood sensors and rain gauges Data clustering to find highly correlated rain gauges Data classification to predict flooding by rainfall data References Preamble In the earlier sections, we&amp;rsquo;ve explored the extensive open data available through Civil IoT Taiwan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.2. Data Access under Spatial or Temporal Conditions</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch3/ch3.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch3/ch3.2/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Data access under temporal conditions Data access under spatial conditions Case study: Is the air quality here worse than there? Import data Remove invalid data Calculate distance Pandas package Results References This article will explore the Civil IoT Taiwan project&amp;rsquo;s data, focusing on how it changes over time and location. We&amp;rsquo;ll provide a straightforward example with a focus on monitoring air quality. The topics covered will include:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4.2. Time Series Data Forecast</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch4/ch4.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch4/ch4.2/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Goal Package Installation and Importing Data Access Air Quality Data Water Level Data Meteorological Data Data Preprocessing Stationary Evaluation Data Forecast ARIMA SARIMAX auto_arima Prophet LSTM Holt-Winter Comparison References The previous chapter has introduced various methods of processing time series data, including visual presentation of data, decomposition of time series data, etc. In this chapter, we will further extract the characteristics of these data and use various predictive models to find the law of the data and predict the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5.2. Geospatial Analysis</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/ch5.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/ch5.2/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Voronoi diagram Convex hull Clustering Kernel density Spatial interpolation Inverse Distance Weighting Kriging Nearest neighbor Interpolation Contour Profile References Environmental microsensors scattered throughout our surroundings play a crucial role in gathering information. This data aids us in making informed decisions and taking appropriate actions. A key aspect of this process involves understanding the spatial relationships between sensor stations when analyzing their data. These station locations can reveal geometric patterns or form spatial clusters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.2. Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch6/ch6.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch6/ch6.2/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Anomaly Detection Framework Types of abnormal events Possible causes of abnormal events Case Study Package Installation and Importing Initialization and Data Access Find nearby sensors Time slicing every five minutes Average the sensing values of nearby sensors every time slice Abnormal event judgements Implementation of the Malfunction Detection module Implementation of the Real-time Emission Detection module Implementation of the Device Ranking module References Anomaly Detection Framework In various countries and cities, we&amp;rsquo;ve seen the successful implementation of expansive networks for monitoring air quality at a micro level.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4.3. Time Series Data Clustering</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch4/ch4.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch4/ch4.3/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Goal Package Installation and Importing Data Access and Preprocessing Data Clustering Fast Fourier Transform Wavelet Transform References Cluster analysis is a commonly used data processing method in data science, and its primary purpose is to find similar clusters in the data. After cluster analysis, data with similar attributes are clustered together for ease of use, and researchers can perform deeper analysis and processing on data with similar characteristics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.3. Joint Data Calibration</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch6/ch6.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch6/ch6.3/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Package Installation and Importing Initialization and Data Access Data Preprocessing Calibration Model Establishment and Validation Best Calibration Model of the Day Calibration Results References In this article, we&amp;rsquo;re going to look at how air quality data from Civil IoT Taiwan can be used. We&amp;rsquo;ll explain how we can calibrate two types of air quality sensors using data science, so they work together better. This helps us get a more complete picture of air quality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.3. Leafmap Applications</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/ch7.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/ch7.3/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Package Installation and Importing Data Access Leafmap Basics Basic Data Presentation Cluster Data Presentation Change Leafmap Basemap Integrate OSM Resources Heatmap Presentation Split Window Presentation Leafmap for Web Applications Conclusion References In earlier sections, we showed you how to analyze geographic data using programming and how to use GIS (Geographic Information System) software for basic analysis and display of this data. Now, we&amp;rsquo;re going to teach you how to use Leafmap in Python for GIS tasks, and how to develop websites with Streamlit.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>