<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ming-Kuang Chung on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</title>
    <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/authors/ming-kuang-chung/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ming-Kuang Chung on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-tw</language><atom:link href="https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/authors/ming-kuang-chung/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>5.1. Geospatial Filtering</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/ch5.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/ch5.1/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Intersect Buffer Multi-ring buffer Distance matrix Brief Summary In the past, if we’re curious about geospatial phenomena such as air quality, earthquakes or floods, we rely on information provided by public sectors or experts to grasp the spatial domain and intensity of phenomena.
Suppose that we want to see the air quality in neighborhoods of our house, one important information source would be the Taiwan Air Quality Monitoring Network run by Environmental Protection Administration Executive Yuan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.1. QGIS Application</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/ch7.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/ch7.1/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Goal QGIS Basic Operation Data Preparation GeoJSON Output Data Filter and Change Colors Export Thematic Maps Example 2: Distribution of Emergency Shelters Conclusion References QGIS is a free geographic information system. In addition to presenting the data collected by users in the form of geographic data, users can also process, analyze and integrate geospatial data through QGIS, and draw thematic maps. In this article, we will use QGIS to assist in the analysis and presentation of PM2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5.2. Geospatial Analysis</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/ch5.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/ch5.2/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Voronoi diagram Convex hull Clustering Kernel density Spatial interpolation Inverse Distance Weighting Kriging Nearest neighbor Interpolation Contour Profile References Microsensors that are widespread in the environment help us obtain environmental information, making decisions and taking actions accordingly. Therefore, it’s fundamental for us to clearly understand the spatial relationships between stations when analyzing data of stations. Apart from that the location of stations itself may form certain geometric structures or spatial clusters, we can also estimate the values where there’s no stations according to the location of stations and their value differences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.2. Tableau Application</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/ch7.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/ch7.2/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Goal Data Source Tableau Basic Operation Data Import Worksheet Introduction Tableau Example 1: Spatio-temporal Distribution of Air Quality Data Spatial Distribution Graph Time Series Graph Tableau Example 2: Disaster Notification Dashboard Disaster data format conversion Dashboard size Add worksheets to a dashboard Add interactions Interacting multiple worksheet Additional information Story Conclusion References Data visualization transforms data into graphical formats, making it easier to understand and interpret. Different graph types are better suited for various data sets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.3. Leafmap Applications</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/ch7.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/ch7.3/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Package Installation and Importing Data Access Leafmap Basics Basic Data Presentation Cluster Data Presentation Change Leafmap Basemap Integrate OSM Resources Heatmap Presentation Split Window Presentation Leafmap for Web Applications Conclusion References In earlier sections, we showed you how to analyze geographic data using programming and how to use GIS (Geographic Information System) software for basic analysis and display of this data. Now, we&amp;rsquo;re going to teach you how to use Leafmap in Python for GIS tasks, and how to develop websites with Streamlit.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>