<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ling-Jyh Chen on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</title>
    <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/authors/ling-jyh-chen/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ling-Jyh Chen on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-tw</language><atom:link href="https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/authors/ling-jyh-chen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2.1. Material Architecture</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch2/ch2.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch2/ch2.1/</guid>
      <description>This comprehensive set of materials on Civil IoT Taiwan data application is organized into seven distinct themes, each focusing on different aspects of data utilization and analysis. Here&amp;rsquo;s an overview of each theme:
Introduction: This section lays the foundation by introducing the Civil IoT Taiwan Project. It highlights the project&amp;rsquo;s achievements over the years and its significant impact on water resources, air quality, earthquake, and disaster prevention and relief. Through various materials, videos, and success stories, learners gain a profound understanding of the project&amp;rsquo;s relevance to everyday life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2.2. Material Tools</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch2/ch2.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch2/ch2.2/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Programming Language - Python Development Platform – Google Colab References Programming Language - Python This material is tailored for those interested in harnessing data from the Civil IoT for public welfare purposes, using Python — a language that&amp;rsquo;s highly favored in the data science community. The course is structured to offer an engaging, hands-on learning experience. It breaks down complex topics into manageable sections, guiding participants through practical applications of Civil IoT data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.3. Leafmap Applications</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/ch7.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/ch7.3/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Package Installation and Importing Data Access Leafmap Basics Basic Data Presentation Cluster Data Presentation Change Leafmap Basemap Integrate OSM Resources Heatmap Presentation Split Window Presentation Leafmap for Web Applications Conclusion References In earlier sections, we showed you how to analyze geographic data using programming and how to use GIS (Geographic Information System) software for basic analysis and display of this data. Now, we&amp;rsquo;re going to teach you how to use Leafmap in Python for GIS tasks, and how to develop websites with Streamlit.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>