<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>5. Spatial Data Analysis on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</title>
    <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 5. Spatial Data Analysis on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-tw</language><atom:link href="https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>5.1. Geospatial Filtering</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/ch5.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/ch5.1/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Intersect Buffer Multi-ring buffer Distance matrix Brief Summary In the past, if we’re curious about geospatial phenomena such as air quality, earthquakes or floods, we rely on information provided by public sectors or experts to grasp the spatial domain and intensity of phenomena.
Suppose that we want to see the air quality in neighborhoods of our house, one important information source would be the Taiwan Air Quality Monitoring Network run by Environmental Protection Administration Executive Yuan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5.2. Geospatial Analysis</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/ch5.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/ch5.2/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Voronoi diagram Convex hull Clustering Kernel density Spatial interpolation Inverse Distance Weighting Kriging Nearest neighbor Interpolation Contour Profile References Environmental microsensors scattered throughout our surroundings play a crucial role in gathering information. This data aids us in making informed decisions and taking appropriate actions. A key aspect of this process involves understanding the spatial relationships between sensor stations when analyzing their data. These station locations can reveal geometric patterns or form spatial clusters.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>