<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>5. Spatial Data Analysis on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</title>
    <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 5. Spatial Data Analysis on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-tw</language><atom:link href="https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>5.1. Geospatial Filtering</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/ch5.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/ch5.1/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Intersect Buffer Multi-ring buffer Distance matrix Brief Summary In the past, if we’re curious about geospatial phenomena such as air quality, earthquakes or floods, we rely on information provided by public sectors or experts to grasp the spatial domain and intensity of phenomena.
Suppose that we want to see the air quality in neighborhoods of our house, one important information source would be the Taiwan Air Quality Monitoring Network run by Environmental Protection Administration Executive Yuan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5.2. Geospatial Analysis</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/ch5.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/ch5.2/</guid>
      <description>{{ &amp;lt; toc &amp;gt; }}
Microsensors that are widespread in the environment help us obtain environmental information, making decisions and taking actions accordingly. Therefore, it’s fundamental for us to clearly understand the spatial relationships between stations when analyzing data of stations. Apart from that the location of stations itself may form certain geometric structures or spatial clusters, we can also estimate the values where there’s no stations according to the location of stations and their value differences.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>