<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>intermediate on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</title>
    <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/levels/intermediate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in intermediate on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-tw</language><atom:link href="https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/levels/intermediate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>6.1. Machine Learning Preliminaries</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch6/ch6.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch6/ch6.1/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Preamble Classification Clustering Package Installation and Importing Case 1: Location Type Classification of Air Quality Sensors Data Cleansing Outlier removal Train data and test data Using the pre-built Sklearn models Case 2: Clustering of Air Quality Sensors Data download and preprocessing Dynamic Time Warping (DTW) K-Mean clustering Correlation between data clusters and geographical locations Correlation between data clusters and wind directions Case 3: Clustering and Classification Application of Water and Meteorological Data Data download and preprocessing Correlation of flood sensors and rain gauges Data clustering to find highly correlated rain gauges Data classification to predict flooding by rainfall data References Preamble In the earlier sections, we&amp;rsquo;ve explored the extensive open data available through Civil IoT Taiwan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.2. Data Access under Spatial or Temporal Conditions</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch3/ch3.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch3/ch3.2/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Data access under temporal conditions Data access under spatial conditions Case study: Is the air quality here worse than there? Import data Remove invalid data Calculate distance Pandas package Results References This article will explore the Civil IoT Taiwan project&amp;rsquo;s data, focusing on how it changes over time and location. We&amp;rsquo;ll provide a straightforward example with a focus on monitoring air quality. The topics covered will include:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4.2. Time Series Data Forecast</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch4/ch4.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch4/ch4.2/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Goal Setting Up the Environment Data Access Air Quality Data Water Level Data Meteorological Data Data Preprocessing Stationary Evaluation Data Forecast ARIMA SARIMAX auto_arima Prophet LSTM Holt-Winter Comparison References In the last chapter, we explored different ways to handle and understand data that changes over time, like creating visual representations and breaking down the data into smaller parts. This chapter will delve deeper into these data sets, focusing on identifying their unique features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5.2. Geospatial Analysis</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/ch5.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/ch5.2/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Voronoi diagram Convex hull Clustering Kernel density Spatial interpolation Inverse Distance Weighting Kriging Nearest neighbor Interpolation Contour Profile References Environmental microsensors scattered throughout our surroundings play a crucial role in gathering information. This data aids us in making informed decisions and taking appropriate actions. A key aspect of this process involves understanding the spatial relationships between sensor stations when analyzing their data. These station locations can reveal geometric patterns or form spatial clusters.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>