<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>7. System Integration and Applications on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</title>
    <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 7. System Integration and Applications on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-tw</language><atom:link href="https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>7.1. QGIS Application</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/ch7.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/ch7.1/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Goal QGIS Basic Operation Data Preparation GeoJSON Output Data Filter and Change Colors Export Thematic Maps Example 2: Distribution of Emergency Shelters Conclusion References QGIS is a free geographic information system. In addition to presenting the data collected by users in the form of geographic data, users can also process, analyze and integrate geospatial data through QGIS, and draw thematic maps. In this article, we will use QGIS to assist in the analysis and presentation of PM2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.2. Tableau Application</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/ch7.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/ch7.2/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Goal Data Source Tableau Basic Operation Data Import Worksheet Introduction Tableau Example 1: Spatio-temporal Distribution of Air Quality Data Spatial Distribution Graph Time Series Graph Tableau Example 2: Disaster Notification Dashboard Disaster data format conversion Dashboard size Add worksheets to a dashboard Add interactions Interacting multiple worksheet Additional information Story Conclusion References Data visualization is a method of expressing data in a graphical way, which can help us to have a better understanding of the data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.3. Leafmap Applications</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/ch7.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/ch7.3/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Package Installation and Importing Data Access Leafmap Basics Basic Data Presentation Cluster Data Presentation Change Leafmap Basemap Integrate OSM Resources Heatmap Presentation Split Window Presentation Leafmap for Web Applications Conclusion References In the previous chapters, we have demonstrated how to use programming languages to analyze data on geographic attributes, and we have also demonstrated how to use GIS software for simple geographic data analysis and presentation. Next, we will introduce how to use the Leafmap suite in Python language for GIS applications, and the Streamlit suite for website development.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>