<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Huei-Jun Kao on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</title>
    <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/authors/huei-jun-kao/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Huei-Jun Kao on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-tw</language><atom:link href="https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/authors/huei-jun-kao/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1. Introduction</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch1/</guid>
      <description>1. Introduction Table Of Contents Environment Perception Open Data Civil IoT Taiwan Civil IoT Taiwan Data Service Platform References Environment Perception Since ancient times, human curiosity about the natural world began during the agricultural civilization era, when people would look up to the sky and observe the stars. During the Renaissance in the 16th century, Copernicus proposed the heliocentric theory based on the astronomical data available at the time. Galileo and Newton followed his line of thought, laying the foundation for modern science.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2.1. Material Architecture</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch2/ch2.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch2/ch2.1/</guid>
      <description>This set of materials includes seven themes including &amp;ldquo;Introduction&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Overview of the Materials&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Data Access Method&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Data Analysis in Time Dimension&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Data Analysis in Space Dimension&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Data Applications&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;System Applications&amp;rdquo;. The major themes are described as follows:
Introduction: We introduce the core of the entire project - &amp;ldquo;Civil IoT Taiwan Project,&amp;rdquo; including various achievements of the project in the past few years, as well as its open data in water resources, air quality, earthquakes, and disaster prevention and relief fields.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2.2. Material Tools</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch2/ch2.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch2/ch2.2/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Programming Language - Python Development Platform – Google Colab References Programming Language - Python This material is tailored for those interested in harnessing data from the Civil IoT for public welfare purposes, using Python — a language that&amp;rsquo;s highly favored in the data science community. The course is structured to offer an engaging, hands-on learning experience. It breaks down complex topics into manageable sections, guiding participants through practical applications of Civil IoT data.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>