<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quen Luo on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</title>
    <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/authors/quen-luo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Quen Luo on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-tw</language><atom:link href="https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/authors/quen-luo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>6.2. Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch6/ch6.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch6/ch6.2/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Anomaly Detection Framework Types of abnormal events Possible causes of abnormal events Case Study Package Installation and Importing Initialization and Data Access Find nearby sensors Time slicing every five minutes Average the sensing values of nearby sensors every time slice Abnormal event judgements Implementation of the Malfunction Detection module Implementation of the Real-time Emission Detection module Implementation of the Device Ranking module References Anomaly Detection Framework In various countries and cities, we&amp;rsquo;ve seen the successful implementation of expansive networks for monitoring air quality at a micro level.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.3. Joint Data Calibration</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch6/ch6.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch6/ch6.3/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Package Installation and Importing Initialization and Data Access Data Preprocessing Calibration Model Establishment and Validation Best Calibration Model of the Day Calibration Results References In this article, we&amp;rsquo;re going to look at how air quality data from Civil IoT Taiwan can be used. We&amp;rsquo;ll explain how we can calibrate two types of air quality sensors using data science, so they work together better. This helps us get a more complete picture of air quality.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>