<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>beginner on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</title>
    <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/levels/beginner/</link>
    <description>Recent content in beginner on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-tw</language><atom:link href="https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/levels/beginner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1. Introduction</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch1/</guid>
      <description>1. Introduction Table Of Contents Environment Perception Open Data Civil IoT Taiwan Civil IoT Taiwan Data Service Platform References Environment Perception Human beings are full of curiosity about the changes in the natural world, which can probably trace back to the activities of ancient agricultural civilizations, looking up at the stars and stargazing at night. By the Renaissance in the 16th century AD, Copernicus deduced the &amp;ldquo;heliocentric theory&amp;rdquo; based on the existing astronomical data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2. Overview of the Materials</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch2/</guid>
      <description>2. Overview of the Materials In this topic, we will introduce the overall structure of the developed materials of Civil IoT Taiwan Open Data, as well as the programming language Python and the development platform Google Colab used in the materials. In addition to conceptual descriptions, we also provide a large number of extended learning resources from shallow to deep, so that interested readers can further explore and learn according to their own needs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4. Time Series Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch4/</guid>
      <description>4. Time Series Data Analysis In this topic, we will introduce time series data analysis methods for IoT data. We will develop the following three units for a more in-depth exploration by using the Civil IoT Taiwan Data Service Platform.
4.1. Time Series Data ProcessingWe use the sensing data of Civil IoT Taiwan Data Service Platform to guide readers to understand the use of moving average, perform periodic analysis of time series data, and then disassemble the time series data into long-term trends, seasonal changes and residual fluctuations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7. System Integration and Applications</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/</guid>
      <description>7. System Integration and Applications In this theme, we will focus on the integration and application of the Civil IoTTaiwan Open Data and other application software, and through the professional functions of other application software, to further deepen and develop the value of the Civil IoT Taiwan Open Data.
7.3. Leafmap ApplicationsWe introduce the capability of leafmap package to use different types of data for geographic information representation and spatial analysis in Civil IoT Taiwan Data Service Platform, and demonstrate the combination of leafmap and streamlit packages to build Web GIS applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2.1. Material Architecture</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch2/ch2.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch2/ch2.1/</guid>
      <description>This set of materials includes seven themes including &amp;ldquo;Introduction&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Overview of the Materials&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Data Access Method&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Data Analysis in Time Dimension&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Data Analysis in Space Dimension&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Data Applications&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;System Applications&amp;rdquo;. The major themes are described as follows:
Introduction: We introduce the core of the entire project - &amp;ldquo;Civil IoT Taiwan Project&amp;rdquo;, including various achievements of the project in the past few years, as well as its open data, covering water resources, air quality, earthquakes, and disaster prevention and relief fields, which can bring daily life various applications and services in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4.1. Time Series Data Processing</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch4/ch4.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch4/ch4.1/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Goal Package Installation and Importing Data Access Air Quality Data Water Level Data Meteorological Data Data Visualization Data Resample Moving Average Multi-line Charts Calendar Heatmap Data Quality Inspection Outlier Detection Change Point Detection) Missing Data Handling Data Decomposition References Time series data is data formed in the order of appearance in time. Usually, the time interval in the data will be the same (for example, one data every five minutes, or one data per hour), and the application fields are quite wide, such as financial information, space engineering, signal processing, etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2.2. Material Tools</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch2/ch2.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch2/ch2.2/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Programming Language - Python Development Platform – Google Colab References Programming Language - Python The subject of this material is the data application of Civil IoT Taiwan. This set of articles will use Python, a programming language commonly used in the data science community, as the main programming language, and adopt an easy-to-understand demonstration method to guide you to read while doing it, step-by-step into the content of each chapter of the topic, and obtain first-hand experience with Civil IoT Taiwan data applications, and the ability to draw inferences from other data science topics in the future.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>