<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</title>
    <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/tags/introduction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Introduction on Tutorial for CIoT Open Data Applications</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-tw</language><atom:link href="https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/tags/introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1. Introduction</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch1/</guid>
      <description>1. Introduction Table Of Contents Environment Perception Open Data Civil IoT Taiwan Civil IoT Taiwan Data Service Platform References Environment Perception Since ancient times, human curiosity about the natural world began during the agricultural civilization era, when people would look up to the sky and observe the stars. During the Renaissance in the 16th century, Copernicus proposed the heliocentric theory based on the astronomical data available at the time. Galileo and Newton followed his line of thought, laying the foundation for modern science.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2. Overview of the Materials</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch2/</guid>
      <description>2. Overview of the Materials In this topic, we will introduce the overall structure of the developed materials of Civil IoT Taiwan Open Data, as well as the programming language Python and the development platform Google Colab used in the materials. In addition to conceptual descriptions, we also provide a large number of extended learning resources from shallow to deep, so that interested readers can further explore and learn according to their own needs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3. Data Access</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch3/</guid>
      <description>3. Data Access In this topic, we will describe how to directly access the data of the Civil IoT Taiwan Data Service Platform using simple Python syntax through the pyCIOT package. To gain a deeper understanding of the different ways to access data with examples, we divide this topic into two units for a more in-depth introduction:
3.1. Basic Data Access MethodsWe introduce how to obtain water, air, earthquake, and disaster data in the Civil IoT Taiwan Data Service Platform, including the latest sensing data for a single site, a list of all sites, and the latest current sensing data for all sites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4. Time Series Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch4/</guid>
      <description>4. Time Series Data Analysis In this topic, we will introduce time series data analysis methods for IoT data. We will develop the following three units for a more in-depth exploration by using the Civil IoT Taiwan Data Service Platform.
4.1. Time Series Data ProcessingWe use the sensing data of Civil IoT Taiwan Data Service Platform to guide readers to understand the use of moving average, perform periodic analysis of time series data, and then disassemble the time series data into long-term trends, seasonal changes and residual fluctuations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5. Spatial Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch5/</guid>
      <description>5. Spatial Data Analysis In this topic, we introduce a series of spatial data processing and analysis methods according to the geospatial characteristics of IoT data. Through the use of the Civil IoT Taiwan Data Service Platform, we will develop the following units for a more in-depth introduction.
5.1. Geospatial FilteringWe use Civil IoT Taiwan&amp;#39;s earthquake and disaster prevention and relief data and filter the data of specific administrative areas by overlaying the administrative area boundary map obtained from the government open data platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6. Data Applications</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch6/</guid>
      <description>6. Data Applications In this topic, we will focus on derivative applications using Civil IoT Taiwan open data. We strengthen the value and application services of Civil IoT Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s open data by importing other library packages and analysis algorithms. The units we expect to develop include:
6.1. Machine Learning PreliminariesWe use air quality and water level data, combined with weather observations, using machine learning for data classification and data grouping. We demonstrate the standard process of machine learning and introduce how to further predict data through data classification and how to further explore data through data grouping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7. System Applications</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch7/</guid>
      <description>7. System Integration and Applications In this theme, we will focus on the integration and application of the Civil IoTTaiwan Open Data and other application software, and through the professional functions of other application software, to further deepen and develop the value of the Civil IoT Taiwan Open Data.
7.1. QGIS ApplicationWe introduce the presentation of geographic data using the QGIS system, and use the data from Civil IoT Taiwan as an example to perform geospatial analysis by clicking and dragging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2.1. Material Architecture</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch2/ch2.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch2/ch2.1/</guid>
      <description>This comprehensive set of materials on Civil IoT Taiwan data application is organized into seven distinct themes, each focusing on different aspects of data utilization and analysis. Here&amp;rsquo;s an overview of each theme:
Introduction: This section lays the foundation by introducing the Civil IoT Taiwan Project. It highlights the project&amp;rsquo;s achievements over the years and its significant impact on water resources, air quality, earthquake, and disaster prevention and relief. Through various materials, videos, and success stories, learners gain a profound understanding of the project&amp;rsquo;s relevance to everyday life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/about/</guid>
      <description>This website provides data application descriptions and examples based on various open data from Civil IoT Taiwan. Please refer to the original website description for the authorization requirements of different available data used on this website. For the Python language packages and software packages used in the program examples provided on this website, please refer to the relevant webpage instructions of each package and software for authorization. The content of articles offered on this site is licensed under CC-BY (https://creativecommons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2.2. Material Tools</title>
      <link>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch2/ch2.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://LearnCIOT.github.io/en/ch2/ch2.2/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents Programming Language - Python Development Platform – Google Colab References Programming Language - Python This material is tailored for those interested in harnessing data from the Civil IoT for public welfare purposes, using Python — a language that&amp;rsquo;s highly favored in the data science community. The course is structured to offer an engaging, hands-on learning experience. It breaks down complex topics into manageable sections, guiding participants through practical applications of Civil IoT data.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>